[
    {
        "front": "こくさい",
        "back": "international",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "けいざい",
        "back": "economics",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "がくぶ",
        "back": "department",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "にゅうがく（する）",
        "back": "entrance / to enter (a school)",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "そうぎょう",
        "back": "to graduate",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "よしゅう",
        "back": "preparation for classes",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふくしゅう",
        "back": "revision",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "たのしむ",
        "back": "to enjoy",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "たのしみにする",
        "back": "to look forward to",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "がんばる",
        "back": "to work hard",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "つもり",
        "back": "intention",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ようちえん",
        "back": "kindergarten (3)",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょうがっこう",
        "back": "primary school (6)",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうがっこう",
        "back": "junior high school (3)",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうとうがっこう",
        "back": "senior high school (3)",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいがく",
        "back": "university (4)",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいがくいん",
        "back": "graduate school (2~5)",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ようちえんじ",
        "back": "kindergarten students",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょうがくせい",
        "back": "primary school students",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうがくせい",
        "back": "junior high school students",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうこうせい",
        "back": "high school students",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいがくせい",
        "back": "university students",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいがくいんせい",
        "back": "graduate students",
        "chapter": "N4 C18"
    }
]